▍2026 辛辛那提 ATP1000 第二轮
蒂兰特 2-6 6-4 6-4 德约科维奇 · 赛后场上采访
Thiago Agustin Tirante of Argentina
阿根廷的蒂亚戈·蒂兰特
with the biggest win of his life.
拿下了他人生最大的一场胜利
He takes down
他掀翻了
the three-time champion here,
这里的三冠王
Novak Djokovic.
德约科维奇
Thiago, huge congratulations.
蒂亚戈 太恭喜你了
Probably the biggest victory of your career.
这大概是你生涯最大的胜利
We saw the emotion behind
我们看到了你的情绪
when you sat on the bench.
在你坐回椅子上的时候
Just tell us what you're going
跟我们说说
through, what you're feeling right now.
你现在是什么感受
Yes, thank you.
好的 谢谢
I think so for for for bigs,
我想是这样
this is my best win of my career.
这是我生涯最好的一场胜利
I think I I I really do a good job inside
我觉得我在场上
the court.
真的做得很好
I manage very well.
我控制得很好
I think the the nervous you know playing
我是说紧张 你知道
against a legend like Novak.
跟德约这样的传奇打球
So yeah I am I
所以 是啊
am now I feel released you know
我现在感觉整个人松下来了
so because it's all
因为整场
so much pressure when you
压力太大了
when you can break so many time
有那么多次机会破发
because I have so many points to break
我拿到了那么多破发点
and I I couldn't so that was I think
可我没能兑现
the key know keep believing in me
所以关键还是相信自己
in my in my forehand in myself
相信我的正手 相信我自己
with my team and and think about it
还有我的团队 然后想着
after the the the match thinking
打完这场之后
about my family my friends
想到我的家人 我的朋友
that is they are in Argentina watching me I
他们都在阿根廷看着我
think They they are really very really happy
我想他们真的非常开心
to I mean to watch me in the TV you know
能在电视上看到我
it's very special for for them and for me
这对他们 对我
as well.
都很特别
So they are in Argentina
他们人在阿根廷
but they are in my head as well.
但也一直在我脑子里
You've spoken so much
你聊过很多次
about your support team and everything
你的团队 还有他们
that they've helped you through this year.
今年怎么一路帮你走过来
What do you feel like are the highlights?
你觉得最关键的是什么
What have they brought you
他们今年
so much this year for you?
给你带来了什么
The confident that they give me.
他们给我的那份信心
I think we are doing really good
我觉得我们做得真的很好
job with my mental health you know
在心理这一块
with my person that help me
有一位专门帮我
with the mental health.
处理心理这一块
So they are they are helping me a lot
他们帮了我很多
and this I think was the key
我觉得这就是今年的关键
for for this year to keep believing in me
就是一直相信我自己
and to listen more my my my team
多听我团队的话
and between the points in the match.
还有比赛里分与分之间
So I think I think I I am I
所以我想
am doing doing the right thing.
我在做对的事